easel.io 2014-10-22

# Easel

Effective Date: June 4, 2012

Easel collects personal information from you, such as name and email address, when you sign up for our service or contact us by email. We also track many of the actions you take on our site in order to improve the service. 

We will not rent, sell, or share your personal information except in accordance with this policy. 

If you no longer choose to use our service, you may delete your account by contacting [support@easel.com](mailto:support@easel.com). 

## Data Privacy

We understand that the data you send to Easel is confidential and we treat it as such. Access will be restricted to the team members you invite, and to certain Easel staff in order to provide support and develop the service. 

## Data Storage

Easel uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run our services. Although Easel owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Easel applications, you retain all rights to your data. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from our servers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to access information when you sign in, store your preferences, to keep you logged in, and to store a limited amount of behavioral data. You can configure your browser to accept or reject these cookies with the drawback that certain features of Easel’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

## Third Party Services

In order to improve the quality of your experience on our site we use several third party services which have access to some of your information including: Olark, Desk.com, Mixpanel, Intercom.io and Google Analytics. For the services that provide an ability to opt out, directions are listed below. 

### Opt out of Mixpanel

You may choose to [opt out of the Mixpanel cookie](https://mixpanel.com/optout/) at any time. 

When you get a new computer, install a new browser, erase or otherwise alter your browser's cookie file (including upgrading certain browsers) you may also clear the cookies in your browser, including the Mixpanel opt-out cookie. 

### Opt out of Google Analytics

Google provides [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=None) which when installed will prevent your browser from sending any data to Google Analytics. 

When you get a new computer, install a new browser you must reinstall the addon to prevent data from being sent to Google Analytics. 

## Non Personally Identifying Information

From time to time, Easel may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

## Disclosure

Easel may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service of our application. 

## Business Transfers

If Easel, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Easel goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Easel may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

## Payment Information

We do not have access to or store personal credit information ("PCI"). Financial transactions are processed through [Stripe](https://stripe.com/) and are subject to its terms and policies. 

## Changes to this privacy policy

We'll let you know about any significant changes by posting a notice on our login page 30 days before they become effective. 

## Questions or comments

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact us by email at [support@easel.io](mailto:support@easel.io).
